export const chapter = "Chapter - 10: Adverb";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What type of adverb is 'beautifully' in the sentence 'She beautifully painted the scenery.'?",
          optionA: "Adverb of Place",
          optionB: "Adverb of Manner",
          optionC: "Adverb of Time",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adverb indicates the frequency of an action in the sentence 'They must attend school daily.'?",
          optionA: "Always",
          optionB: "Daily",
          optionC: "Frequently",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In which sentence is the adverb placed at the beginning of the sentence?",
          optionA: "'She walked on the road purposelessly.'",
          optionB: "'Suddenly, a stone came crashing down the hill.'",
          optionC: "'They finished the task efficiently.'",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What type of adverb is 'yesterday' in the sentence 'They went there yesterday.'?",
          optionA: "Adverb of Time",
          optionB: "Adverb of Manner",
          optionC: "Adverb of Place",
          correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adverb modifies an adjective in the sentence 'You are very clever and smart.'?",
          optionA: "Very",
          optionB: "Clever",
          optionC: "Smart",
          correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
          question: "Where should the adverb 'enough' be placed in a sentence?",
          optionA: "Before the word it modifies",
          optionB: "After the word it modifies",
          optionC: "In the middle of the sentence",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The children enjoyed noisily,' what type of verb does the adverb 'noisily' modify?",
          optionA: "Transitive Verb",
          optionB: "Intransitive Verb",
          optionC: "Auxiliary Verb",
          correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adverb is used to ask questions in the sentence 'Why should you speak so roughly?'?",
          optionA: "Roughly",
          optionB: "So",
          optionC: "Why",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the position of an adverb when it modifies a transitive verb?",
          optionA: "Before the verb",
          optionB: "Between the verb and its direct object",
          optionC: "After the direct object",
          correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the comparative form of the adverb 'late' in the sentence 'Shivani came later than Madhur.'?",
          optionA: "Later",
          optionB: "Late",
          optionC: "Latest",
          correctAnswer: "A",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "An Adverb can modify a Verb, an Adjective, or another Adverb in a sentence; for example: Mohit completed his project ________.",
          optionA: "hastily",
          optionB: "calmly",
          optionC: "rarely",
          correctAnswer: "hastily",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In sentence 2, Adverb very is modifying the Adjective ________ lady.",
          optionA: "tall",
          optionB: "beautiful",
          optionC: "intelligent",
          correctAnswer: "beautiful",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of ________ show the manner how an action is done; for example: suddenly, strongly, proudly.",
          optionA: "Place",
          optionB: "Time",
          optionC: "Manner",
          correctAnswer: "Manner",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Time show the time when an action is done; for example: today, tomorrow, everyday, ________.",
          optionA: "now",
          optionB: "rarely",
          optionC: "never",
          correctAnswer: "now",
        },
        {
          question:
            "An Interrogative Adverb is used to ask a question; for example: where, why, when, ________?",
          optionA: "how",
          optionB: "who",
          optionC: "what",
          correctAnswer: "how",
        },
        {
          question:
            "An Adverb modifies a Verb, an Adjective, or another Adverb in a sentence. It should be placed as near as possible to the word it ________.",
          optionA: "precedes",
          optionB: "follows",
          optionC: "modifies",
          correctAnswer: "modifies",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Most Adverbs of Manner are used in ________ or mid-position.",
          optionA: "beginning-position",
          optionB: "end-position",
          optionC: "middle-position",
          correctAnswer: "end-position",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs showing definite time are placed in the ________ or initial-position.",
          optionA: "middle-position",
          optionB: "end-position",
          optionC: "beginning-position",
          correctAnswer: "end-position",
        },
        {
          question: "Enough is always used ________ the word it modifies.",
          optionA: "before",
          optionB: "after",
          optionC: "between",
          correctAnswer: "after",
        },
        {
          question: "The tiger ran ________ of the three animals.",
          optionA: "faster",
          optionB: "fastly",
          optionC: "more fast",
          correctAnswer: "faster",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "An Adverb can only modify a Verb in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of Time show the place where an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Degree show the quantity or extent of an action.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Interrogative Adverbs are used to make statements rather than asking questions.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs modifying Intransitive Verbs are placed between the Verb and its Direct Object.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Manner are always placed at the beginning of a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs showing definite time are generally placed at the end of a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of Place indicate the frequency of an action.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Enough is always placed before the word it modifies.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs can modify Adjectives and Pronouns in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
